agilone.com 2016-12-02

# Privacy Policy - AgilOne | Customer Data and Engagement Hub

### Privacy Policy

**Effective date: July 6, 2012**

[](https://safeharbor.export.gov/list.aspx)**This privacy policy (this “Policy”) describes the types of information that AgilOne, Inc. (including our affiliates, “AgilOne” or “we”) collects from users of its corporate Web site, www.agilone.com, as well as any Web site that directly links to this Policy when you click on “Privacy” or “Privacy Policy” in the Web site footer (each, a “Site”). Unless otherwise provided in this Policy, this Policy does not cover our offline data practices. This Policy also describes the services we provide to our clients (our “Services”).  To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>**

This Policy is effective as of the date set forth above. We encourage you to check this Policy from time to time. If we make material changes that will affect any personal information that we have already collected from you, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the changes and to give you the opportunity to opt out. Your continued use of this Site constitutes your acceptance of the current posted Policy. If you have questions about our privacy policy, please contact us as provided below.

### Cookies

Cookies are files that Web servers place on an Internet user’s computer that are designed to store basic information and to recognize your browser. As discussed below, our Site employs Cookies in connection with your use of the Site. These Cookies do not store any information that we can use to personally identify you (“Personally Identifiable Information”). As with all Cookies, you can set your browser to notify you before you receive these Cookies so that you have the chance to accept them. You can also set your browser so that it will not accept Cookies.

### Your use of the Site

You can visit and navigate through our Site to information about our company, our Services, and the products offered without telling us who you are and without revealing any information that can personally identify you. As discussed above, out Site does use Cookies and other technology in connection with a hosted Web site analytics service that helps us better understand how our visitors use the Site. We review the anonymous information provided by these uses of Cookies (e.g., browser type, operating system, IP address, Internet domain) to better understand how our visitors navigate through the Site, learn what content is being reviewed, administer the Site, and manage online advertising on the Site. No Personally Identifiable Information is collected through our use of these Cookies.

You may wish to request information about our Services or our company. In order to facilitate the distribution of this content, we may ask you to provide Personally Identifiable Information. Based on the nature of your request, we may also ask for additional information, such as how you anticipate you (or your company) will make use of our Services and how you heard about us. We store the information you provide for archival purposes and for our own marketing purposes if we feel that it is consistent with the nature of the inquiry. We will not use this information for any other purpose unless you give us permission to do so. Again, all of this information is provided by you on a voluntary basis only and is not required in order for you to use and enjoy our Site.

Our Sites may offer opportunities for you to register for free information, seminars, or demonstration copies of our Services. These registration forms are often linked to AgilOne mailing lists, and require users to provide Personally Identifiable Information (such as name and e-mail address), which we use to send users information about our company and our Services. We also use this information to contact site visitors by e-mail for marketing purposes if they have granted us permission (on the mailing list form or other forms on our Site) to send it to them, and for administrative purposes such as providing time and location of seminars. Users may also be contacted by phone or postal mail for marketing purposes.

### Public Forum

We may at times offer you the option to post content to a blog, message board, or chat room. In the course of doing so, you may provide Personally Identifiable Information. You should be aware that any visitor may you’re your postings on a blog, on a message board, or in a chat room. Furthermore, any information that you may post, including your profile information, is available to all users of that blog, message board, or chat room, and thus is neither private nor confidential. We cannot guarantee the security of such information that is disclosed or communicated online in these public areas, and you do so at your own risk. We reserve the right at any time, in our sole discretion, to remove any content that you may post on any blog, message board, or chat room and/or restrict your access to any blog, message board, or chat room. We further reserve the right to republish any user postings from blogs, message boards, or chat rooms elsewhere on the Internet in any format.

Your interactions with the user community programs we have with third party social networking sites such as Facebook may be displayed on this Site and used by us in a manner consistent with this Policy. Your interactions may also be displayed in your social networking profile. These interactions may be viewable by anyone that has access to that profile, depending on your privacy settings with the social networking site. You should review the privacy policies of these social networking sites to understand who may have access to your interactions and how the Site may use them.

### Our Provision of Services to our Clients

AgilOne is a provider of predictive customer intelligence solutions. Our Services include a data storage and computational platform, reporting and business intelligence portal, predictive engine, and integrated list execution solution. Some of our products are offered as application Services, meaning that we host a software application that our clients access via the worldwide web. Each client understands that in the course of providing our Services to it, we collect or receive information about the individual to whom our client directs its marketing messages. Some of the information that we collect and store on our client’s behalf is Personally Identifiable Information. AgilOne may in the course of providing its Services collect data from the internet using web beacon or Stat One. AgilOne may also purchase third party data on the behalf of its client for use by such client.

As between AgilOne and our client, all of the information we receive from our client belongs to our client and not to us. We may use such information only as provided in our written agreement with the individual client. While our specific responsibilities regarding such information are found in these written agreements, we do not allow individual information collected and stored for one client to be accessed or used by any other AgilOne client (or by AgilOne on our own behalf). We reserve a limited right to use our client’s information to compile aggregated statistics, which we use to report such facts as how many emails we have delivered. However, we do not disclose this information in such a way as to enable anyone to identify a client or any individual. Our client agreements also permit us to disclose any information if required by law or court order.

In our client agreements, we require each client to abide by all laws, rules and regulations that are applicable to the Customer’s use of our Services and we promise each client that we will do the same with respect to our provision of Services. We ask each client to post a privacy policy that covers the client’s use of our Services. We also request the client to acquire and maintain all rights that allow us to provide the Services, such as to receive the information that we collect and store on the client’s behalf.

Our Services may use Cookies or other technologies to help our client better analyze their marketing efforts. The technologies we use are often correlated with information that can identify an individual. As with the other information we maintain and process for each of our clients, this information is not used by us except as described above and is not shared with other AgilOne clients.

AgilOne is not responsible for its client’s own privacy policies and makes no representations about their accuracy. If you have questions about our client’s practices, we recommend you check their privacy policies and/or contact them directly.

### Safe Harbor Privacy Statement

AgilOne respects and protects the individual privacy and confidence of our clients, stakeholders, employees, business partners, and others who may use our Services. Protecting consumer privacy is important to AgilOne. AgilOne complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. AgilOne adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement (the “Principles”). To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

If there is any conflict between the provisions of this Policy and the Principles, the Principles shall govern. This Policy outlines our general policy and practices for implementing the Principles, including the types of information we gather, how we use it and the notice and choice affected individuals have regarding our use of and their ability to correct that information

### Payment Card Industry (PCI) Privacy Statement

AgilOne does not accept, store, process or transmit cardholder data, but as part of our platform and services we receive and store personally identifiable information. We acknowledge responsibility for the security of data that we store, process or transmit on behalf of our customers or to the extent that we could impact the security of our customers’ personally identifiable information.

### Data Security

AgilOne takes reasonable steps to protect all data in our possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. For example, the confidentiality of information being transferred on portable media (e.g. laptop, flash drive) or across networks is protected by our use of appropriate encryption techniques.

AgilOne controls and physically protects media and establishes appropriate operating procedures to protect documents, computer media, input/output data and, system documentation from unauthorized disclosure, modification, removal, and destruction.

Prior to disposal, AgilOne checks all items of equipment containing storage media to remove or securely overwrite data and licensed software. Devices containing sensitive information are physically destroyed or the information is destroyed, deleted or overwritten.

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. However, we cannot guarantee the security of data in our possession or data that is on, or transmitted via, the Internet.

With whom we may share your information We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Policy. The information we collect is not shared, rented, or sold to any third-parties. We may provide your information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as responding to your inquiries or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We may also disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;
  * in order to investigate and/or enforce possible violations of our Policy or client agreements; and
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

### Advertising Cookies

As you browse www.agilone.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with www.agilone.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit this [page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

### Enforcement

AgilOne uses a self-assessment approach to assure compliance with this Policy and periodically verifies that the Policy is accurate, comprehensive for the information intended to be covered, prominently displayed, completely implemented and accessible, and in conformity with the Principles.

### Data Integrity

AgilOne processes data in a way that is compatible with and relevant for the purpose for which it was collected or authorized by the owning person. To the extent necessary for those purposes, we take reasonable steps to ensure that data is accurate, complete, current, and reliable for its intended use.

### Changes in our business or privacy policies

As we continue to develop our business, we may sell certain or all of our assets. In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are acquired in a transaction, our visitor information (including your Personally Identifiable Information) may be an asset that is reviewed and transferred. Such a transaction will be disclosed per the guidelines below.

This Policy may be amended from time to time consistent with the requirements of the Safe Harbor. If we decide to revise this Policy, we will post any revised Policy on this Site and/or to other places we deem appropriate so our visitors can be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose it. If, however, we are going to use your Personally Identifiable Information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will post a notice on the Site 30 days in advance of such use.

### Links to other Web sites

The Site may contain links to other Web sites, such as those of our sellers and partners. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other Web sites.

### Children

This Site is not intended to nor does it seek to receive information from children under the age of 13.

### Access or Update Your Information.

We provide you with the opportunity to review, modify, and delete any Personally Identifiable Information that you have previously provided to us pursuant to your visits to our Site. You can send us an email or write to us as set forth below.

### Contact Information

Questions, comments, or complaints regarding this Policy or AgilOne’s data collection and processing practices can be sent to:

Attention: Privacy Officer  
AgilOne  
771 Vaqueros Ave  
Sunnyvale, CA 94085  
Email: [info@agilone.com](mailto:info@agilone.com)  
Phone: (877) 769 3047
